<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<odoo>
    <template id="aboutus_inherit" inherit_id="website.aboutus">
        <xpath expr="//div[hasclass('oe_structure')]" position="replace">
            <div id="wrap" class="oe_structure oe_empty">
                <section id="about-us-savvy">
                    <div class="container">
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-md-12">
                                <h1 class="text-primary">About Us</h1>
                            </div>
                            <div class="col-md-6">
                                <img class="img img-responsive" src="/customer_telus_theme/static/src/image/about_xl/about-us.png"/>
                            </div>
                            <div class="col-md-6">
                                <p>Mobile Savvy, a Telus Authorized Dealer, is one of the largest Telus Dealers in Ontario.
                                </p>
                                <p>Mobile Savvy has 8 locations to serve you better, located in Hamilton, Mississauga, London, 
                                St. Catherines, Niagara Falls and Kitchener.
                                </p>
                                <p>We are an award-winning Telus dealer, dedicated to providing unique wireless solutions that suit 
                                our customer’s needs.
                                </p>
                                <p>This is achieved through our highly experienced and tech savvy staff, whose #1 goal is to take 
                                care of all our customer’s needs. With over 10 years in the telecommunications industry, Mobile Savvy 
                                understands how to create personalized solutions to match your needs. We make purchasing wireless 
                                products easy and simple.
                                </p>
                            </div>
                            <div class="col-md-12">
                                <p>Mobile Savvy also specializes in building a brilliant digital future for small and enterprise 
                                businesses across Canada. But we don’t think of our business customers as customers. We think of each 
                                one as a partner.
                                </p>
                                <p>We pride ourselves on combining service and expertise with innovative products to meet the needs of 
                                your business.
                                </p>
                                <p>Another thing we are really proud of at Mobile Savvy is that we are an inclusive brand. That’s why our 
                                multicultural staff is happy to support customers in a variety of languages. We are also highly integrated 
                                in the local communities we serve and are dedicated to giving back to serve others.
                                </p>
                                <p>We have an Omni Channel location strategy which provides our customers the option to purchase products 
                                or to get service either in store or online.
                                </p>
                                <p>Whatever your wireless needs are, we have the right device, with the right plan and the best price.
                                </p>
                                <p>Visit out locations page to find a location near you or if you have any questions contact us at <a href="mailto:help@mobilesavvy.ca" target="_top">help@mobilesavvy.ca</a>.
                                </p>
                                <h2 class="text-primary">Message from the Owner</h2>
                                <p>On behalf of the wonderful team at Mobile Savvy, I would like to thank you for visiting our website and 
                                stores and most of all, trusting us with your hard-earned business. We are always striving for excellence and 
                                welcome your feedback. If you would like to contact us directly regarding your experience with Mobile Savvy, 
                                please send us an email at <a href="mailto:help@mobilesavvy.ca" target="_top">help@mobilesavvy.ca</a> 
                                and we will get back to you as soon as possible.
                                </p>
                                <p>We look forward to hearing from you,<br/>
Waleed</p>
                            </div>
                            <div class="hidden col-md-12 col-sm-12 text-center mt64 mb64">
                                <div class="col-md-4 col-sm-4">
                                    <img class="img img-responsive img-circle center-block" src="/customer_telus_theme/static/src/image/about_xl/team-1.png"/>
                                    <h3 class="text-primary">Ehab Bakir</h3>
                                    <p>Ehab started In 1995 and provides the leadership needed to maintain our reputaton
                                        and goodwill in the community.
                                    </p>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-md-4 col-sm-4">
                                    <img class="img img-responsive img-circle center-block" src="/customer_telus_theme/static/src/image/about_xl/team-2.png"/>
                                    <h3 class="text-primary">Waleed Salha</h3>
                                    <p>Waleed started in 1995 and provides the leader-ship needed to maintain our
                                        reputaton and good-will In the community.
                                    </p>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-md-4 col-sm-4">
                                    <img class="img img-responsive img-circle center-block" src="/customer_telus_theme/static/src/image/about_xl/team-1.png"/>
                                    <h3 class="text-primary">Tarek Salha</h3>
                                    <p>Ehab started In 1995 and provides the leadership needed to maintain our reputaton
                                        and goodwill in the community.
                                    </p>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </section>
            </div>
        </xpath>
    </template>
</odoo>
